

#### **About Me**

I'm a creative visual designer and programmer focused on branding, social media, asset production, user-experience and motion graphics. I've been involved in creative tecnology projects which have allowed me to design and code my own solutions. I consider myself independent, flexible, reliable, and a problem solver with good teamwork skills.

## **Brand Experience**

Here are some of the most outstanding brands that I had the opportunity to work with:











Microsoft

### **Work Experience**

- POP Digital (2017-today)
  Visual Designer for brands such as
  Microsoft, Oracle, eBay.
- Urbanet Studio (2016-2017)
  Visual Designer for brands such as
  Arizona and Denny's.
- Pictonauta (2016-today)
   Founder and Designer for brands such as Universidad VERITAS.

## **Technical Knowledge**

Adobe CC























## UX/UI tools





# Others







### Foreign Languages



English Level C1. BELT (2019).

## **Programming Languages**



CSS





#### **Education**

- Universidad Nacional Bachelor in Arts & Visual Design.
- Universidad Estatal a Distancia
   Technical Degree in Computer Science.
- O FID Workshop
  App Design & Customer Flow.